Guide to the Lewis and Clark Centennial and American Pacific Exposition and Oriental Fair Records 1894-1933
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- President's Office, Department of Special Events (Theodore Hardee, director), Series 3
  - Performances and special days, general correspondence
    - Huber - Liberati's Band, 1905 (Box-folder 24/7)
      Ingram, R.E. (Reference Gowen and Brown)
      Jury of Awards
      Kern, J.H. from Huber (Delivery of Goods)
      Kern, R.H. (Reference J.B. Montgomery)
      Killie, Charles A. (Reference Stereoptican Lecture on China)
      Kiralfy Venice Company (Statement of Account, "Venice on the Trail”)
      Kruse, Theo (Kruse's Grill Room and Restaurant)
      Lane, Kathrene (Employment)
      Laurent, Bustave (Visit)
      Lee, G.C. (Dismissal)
      Lee, H. Embert (Chinese Empire Reform Association)
      Liberati's Band (Provide Rooms)
    - MacEvoy, J. - Myers, Jefferson, 1905 (Box-folder 24/8)
      MacEvoy, J. (Leaving Town)
      MacKensie, W.R. (Pay Roll Date/Waiter Fees/etc.)
      Mackey, David L. (Reimbursement)
      Maine, C.J. (Reference Names of Secretaries of Conventions)
      Marshall, H.C. (Reference Postponement of Recital)
      McAllen, Dan (Oaks Amusement Park)
      McCready, Mrs. J.T. (Coats Left Behind)
      McDonnell, Mjr. E. (Improper Seating on Grand Stairway/Guards for Garden Fete; Liability)
      Menu Cards
      Merritt, Will C. (Reunion of Residents Meigs County, Ohio)
      McJimsay, E.E. (Reference Senator Warner Visit)
      Model Camp (Reference Cots)
      Montgomery, May (Lost Necklace)
      Myers, Jefferson (Babies Born on 100th Anniversary Day L & C Left St. Louis)
    - New York Club - Rugg, Frederick D., 1905 (Box-folder 24/9)
      New York Club (Cards)
      New York State Commission (New York Building Reservations 9/6, 9/8, 9/13)
      Newton, D. H. (Reference Hotel Accommodations)
      Notice to Public Reference Cost of Admission to Exposition Grounds
      Patchin, Carolyne (Reference Crater Lake Tour)
      Pennsylvania Society (Auditorium Use, June 6, 1905)
      Pindat (Expenses)
      Recommendations for Various Employees
      Reed, Will T. (Endorsement)
      Reid, Robert A. (Booklet: Views of Lewis and Clark Exposition)
      Roberts, M.H., Chief Inspector (Reference Passes)
      Rugg, Frederick D. (The Pain Pyroteching Company)
    - Schnabel, Charles J. - Wortman, Jenni, 1905 (Box-folder 24/10)
      Schnabel, Charles J. (R.W. Wilbur Endorsement)
      Smith, W.G. and Company (Card Engravers)
      Stanyan, Mrs. M. (Letter of Commendation)
      Steever, Colonel E.E. (Commendation)
      Strough, Francis (13, 14 Illustrated Tours/Sermons)
      Thompson, J. R. (Reference Electric Lights)
      Trades League of Philadelphia (Arrival of President Supplee)
      Underwood Typewriter Company (Typewriter Desks/Typewriters)
      Wessinger, Paul (Reference Herman Wise)
      Wilson, D. Summer (Info Request)
      Wittenberg, Herman (Reference Teachers Convention)
      Wood, Major (Governor Invitees to State Day)
      Word, S.B. (Head Janitor)
      Wortman, Jennae A. (Rambling letters regarding her son as representative of the ideal American boy)
  - Printing companies / special events arrangements, 1905; undated (Box-folder 24/11)
  - Requests for contests and shows, 1905 (Box-folder 24/12)
  - Requisitions, 1905 (Box-folder 24/13)
  - Social list, 1905 (Box-folder 24/14)
  - Special attractions
    - Arrangements, 1905 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - General, 1905 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - General, 1905 (Box-folder 25/3)
      Baum, James and Alferetta (The Marvelous Baums)
      Kilpatrick, Charles G. (Kilpatrick's Famous Ride)
      Marsh, Charles (Marveouls Marsh)
    - National Theatrical Exchange, 1905 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Potential Acts, 1905 (Box-folder 25/5)
      Includes illustrated letterhead from J. S. Connolly (Duel to the Death); and photograph of roller coaster. See also following folder.
    - Potential Acts—Illustrated Letterhead, 1905 (Box-folder 115/2)
      Herr Granada and Miss Alma Fedora, Aerial Wonders
      "K. R. Moore in a new and original act Monkawire."
      Legare's New Mammoth Spiral Tower
      Loretta Twins Trio
      Prof. A. Alfreno (high wire act)
    - Rejection letters, 1905 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Speedy, Kearney P. (high diver, illustrated letterhead), 1905 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - War vessels, 1905 (Box-folder 25/8)
  - Special cities days, 1905 (Box-folder 25/9)
  - Special cities week
    - Arizona, 1905 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - British Columbia, 1905 (Box-folder 25/11)
    - California, A-Z, 1905 (Box-folder 25/12)
    - California, general, 1905 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - Colorado, 1905 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - Idaho, 1905 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - Utah - Wyoming, 1905 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Washington, general, 1905 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Washington, A-N, 1905 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Washington, O-Z, 1905 (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Special Cities Week—Statistics, 1905; undated (Box-folder 26/4)
  - State Commision and general correspondence, 1905 (Box-folder 26/5)
  - Various days
    - General, A-D, 1905 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - General, E-K, 1905 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - General, L-N, 1905 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - General, O-R, 1905 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - General, S-Z, 1905 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Baby Day, 1905 (Box-folder 26/11)
    - Geographical, 1905 (Box-folder 26/12)
    - Labor Day / Music Day, 1905 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Newsboys' Day, 1905 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Pioneer Day, 1905 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Professions Day, 1905 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Public Schools' Day / Private Schools' Day, 1905 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Scandanavian Day / Eureka Cadets, 1905 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - States' Days, A-D, 1905 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - States' Days, F-L, 1905 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - States' Days, M, 1905 (Box-folder 27/9-10)
    - States' Days, O-R, 1905 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - States' Days, S-T, 1905 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - States' Days, U-W, 1905 (Box-folder 28/1)
- President's Office, Department of Special Events, Bureau of Athletics, Series 4
  Includes correspondence of H. W. Kerrigan, Manger of Athletics.
  See also Series 3, Department of Special Events—Athletics, above.
  - Blank entry forms, 1905 (Box-folder 28/2)
    Reliance Athletic Club, May 30, 1905
    A.A.U. Junior National Championships, Friday, Aug. 4, 1905
    Amateur Athletic Union, Saturday, Aug. 5, 1905
  - Completed entry forms, 1905 (Box-folder 28/3)
    YMCA Medals
    Winners in Soldiers Field Meet
    Handicap Events, June 10
    Official Entry Forms Completed
  - Correspondence, general
    - Adam, James - Averill, E. F., 1905 (Box-folder 28/4)
      Adam, James, Ladysmith Basketball Team, Ladysmith, B.C.
      Adams, Dal G., Cornelius, Oregon (Wrestling Championships)
      Ainsworth, J.C. (Reference Trophy)
      Allen and Lewis (Trophy Sketch)
      Allen, Forrest C. (Kansas City Athletic Club)
      Amateur Baseball (See Hart, Geo.)
      Ambrose, J.M. (Reference Pass for Swimming Championship)
      American Gymnasia Company
      Anderson, Edw. Frank, Carson, Washington (Log Rolling Contest)
      Anderson, W.L. (Gymnastic Championship)
      Averill, E.F., Willamette University (College Baseball Tournament)
    - Babbit, O. M. - Boyd, Hugh, 1905 (Box-folder 28/5)
      Babbitt, O.M., YMCA, Portland (Program and Info Request)
      Bates, Geo. W. (Trophy)
      Beach, F.L. (Reference Gold Medal)
      Bean, Willard (Reference Basketball Games)
      Beckett, A.H.E (Reference Rifle Shoot)
      Beissel, E. (Reference Bill to Move Boats)
      Betrand, A.A., Dolphin Swimming and Boating Club
      Bigney, Chas (Diving Contests)
      Bish [?] (cryptic telegram)
      Blair & Adam (Ladysmith, B.C., Basketball and Football Team)
      Blase, John W. (Post Card, Underwater Swimming)
      Bogarders, Irving (Seattle Football Team)
      Boyd, Hugh, Hill Military Academy (Races)
    - Brandon, Charled D. - Butterfield Bros., 1905 (Box-folder 28/6)
      Brandon, Charles D. (Basketball Tournament)
      Brockton Point Athletic Club (Reference Entry/Fees)
      Brooklyn Teams Entries
      Brown, Everett C., Chicago Athletic Association
      Brown, Fred, Astoria, Oregon (Reference Fair Visit/Horse Races)
      Bruchler, H.J., Aldrich Bakery, Chicago (Info Request)
      Burtner, R.D., YMCA, Salt Lake City (Basket Ball Championship)
      Butterfield Bros. (Medals and Cups)
    - Caldwell, R. B. - Clyde, Fred, 1905 (Box-folder 28/7)
      Caldwell, R.B. (Telegram Reference Portland Visit)
      Camp, Walter, Colliers Weekly (Event Promotion)
      Campbell, W.P., Chemawa Indian School (Native American Sports/Medals)
      Carroll, James, Tacoma Athletic Club
      Cau Hilton, Victoria, B.C. (Reference Cricket Events)
      Century Athletic Club (Wm. Brown, Oakland, Calif.)
      Chandler, W.D. (Try-out for Games/Pass)
      Chapin, W.H. (Post Card Reference Meeting)
      Chicago Tribune (Reference Amateur Athletic Union Games)
      Christie, W.M., Trainer, University of California
      City Department of Schools
      Clark, Emery, Boston Athletic Association (Entry Blanks)
      Clarkson, Major T.S. (Complimentary Ticket)
      Clawson, Spencer (Info Request)
      Cleland, T.H., Ladd and Tilton (Hand Ball Committee)
      Cleland, W.A., Portland Commercial Club (Invitation)
      Closset, Joseph (Reference Joseph Closset Trophy)
      Clyde, Fred, South Bend, Washington (Associated Football Tournament)
    - Coe, W. W. - Cronan, Jno., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 28/8)
      Coe, W.W. (Entered in 16-lb Shot Put)
      Condon, J.J. (Association Football Tournament)
      Conibear, H.B., University of Montana (Programs/Music and Special Attractions for Events)
      Connell, L.B., Woodlawn, Oregon (Reference 100-yard Dash)
      Cook, C.E., 14th Infantry BB Team
      Corbett, Henry Ladd ($25 Silver Cup for Tennis Tournament)
      Corcoran, P.C. (Handicap Games)
      Corey, A.L., Care Chicago Athletic Club (Reference Events)
      Cox, Alpha, Whitman College (Entry in Race Events)
      Craig, Oscar J. (Telegram)
      Cronan, Jno. E. (Reference Officiating)
    - Darby, Walter - Dyment, Colvin, 1905 (Box-folder 28/9)
      Darby, Walter F. (Reference Events)
      Dates and Lists of Various Events
      Davison, F.B. (Vacancy/Passes)
      DeForest, Byron (Programs and Info Request Reference Kiely)
      Degler, Silas, Track Manager, Seattle High School (Reference Relay Races)
      Dieges & Clust (Requisition for AAU Championship Medals) 1 of 2
      Dieges & Clust (Requisition for AAU Championship Medals) 2 of 2
      Directors and Banks, List of (Requested to Donate Cups)
      Donaldson, H., Editor The Automobile (Reference Auto Races)
      Douthitt, A.G., YMCA, Seattle (Programs and Events)
      Dowd, W.F. (Seattle Athletic Club Reference Trophies)
      Dresser, F. (F. Dresser Trophy)
      Duffy, Ed. (Reference Pass)
      Dunne, T.M. (Appointment as Chairman Hand Ball Committee)
      Dyment, Colvin V. (Football Tournament)
    - Easton, George - Friday program, 1905 (Box-folder 28/10)
      Easton, Geo. A. (Interscholastic Football contest)
      Edmondson, H. (Inquiry Reference Entry Blanks AAU)
      Edwards, T.A. (Entrance Fee/Schedule of Events)
      Egloffstein, Von (Appointment as Chairman, Fencing Committee)
      Ellison, John (Entry Blanks/Program)
      Ely, Ben C. (Pass)
      Facey, J. Frank, New England Association of the Amateur Athletic Union
      Fagan, J.E., B.P.A.C. (NPAAAChampionship)
      Ferrin, Holman (Reference Public School Events)
      Field, Henry W. (Programs/Athletic Events)
      Fleischner, I.N. (Trophy)
      Flowers, John B. (Inquiry Reference Olympic Games/Races)
      Fly Casting Tournament
      Foster, Thos. (Reference Horse Team in Races)
      Fowler, R.A., Cambridge, Massachusetts (Marathon Race)
      Frank, Edgar (Appointment as Chairman, Boxing, Gym and Wrestling Committee)
      Freeman, D.C. (Application for Passes)
      French Football Club (List of Players)
      Friday Program
    - Gardella, James - Gunn, A. B., 1905 (Box-folder 28/11)
      Gardella, James (Walking Events)
      Gates, H.W., Pacific University (Order of Events/North Pacific Championship Games))
      Gayness, Stuart (Tennis Events)
      Geach, John R. (Info Request)
      Gebhardt, Albert E., Oregon Fish and Game Association (Appointment, Chairman Fly Casting)
      Gilbert, A.C. (Wrestling Championship)
      Gill, Harry L. (Info Request)
      Glarner, Andrew (List of California Athletes/Various topics)
      Goldsmith, A.S., Seattle Athletic Club (NPAAA)
      Goode, Henry W., Correspondence with Kerrigan
      Goss, W.A., Chairman, L & C Tennis Committee (Various/Topics)
      Gunn, A.B., Buffalo, New York (Entry Blanks)
    - Hall, George - Hardee memo, 1905 (Box-folder 28/12)
      Hall, Geo, Mck., YMCA, Buffalo, New York (Entry Blanks)
      Hall, Hammond (Reference Trophy/Medals)
      Hanno, Henry (Appointment as Chair sub-Committee)
      Hardee/Kerrigan Correspondence
      Hardee Memo Reference Sale of Other Programs at Fair
    - Hart, George - Hawk, Alvin, 1905 (Box-folder 28/13)
      Hart, Geo (Appointment as Chair Amateur Base Ball Committee)
      Hartson, clifford (Rugby Football Matches)
      Hastings, George (Entries, Highland School)
      Hauser, Herbert, Secretary, PAA (Various Topics)
      Hawk, Alvin (Entry Blanks)
    - Healer, Roy - Hinchman, W. B., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 28/14)
      Healer, Roy (Pole Vault Entry)
      Heinrich, Joe (Enter Wrestling Tournament)
      Heitkemper, G. and Company (Reference Medals)
      Hempel, Walter, Pomona College (Various Topics)
      Hemphill, J.W., Seattle High School Athletic Association
      Herdman, H.H. (Appointment as Chair NAAA Championship Meet/Protesting Roy Heater)
      Herdt, Alfred (Basket Ball Team)
      Herman, G.K. (Telegram Reference Illinois Club)
      Hicks, Fred N. (Reference Eastern Entries)
      Hill Military Academy (Event Entries)
      Hilton, E.W. Carr (Reference Cricket Matches)
      Hinchman, W.B., President Pacific Athletic Association
    - Hobbis, Elsdale - Hutchinson, William, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 29/1)
      Hobbis, Elsdale H., Victoria, B.C. (Program/Bulletin)
      Holbrook, Sam, MAAAC (Hand Ball Committee)
      Holladay, Ben (Appointment as Chair, Automobile Contests)
      Holman School Entries
      Holzell, C.C. (NPAAA Games)
      Honeman Hardware Company (Programs)
      Honeyman, Walter (Reference Passes/Appointment as Chair LaCrosse Committee)
      Horan, John C., Oregon Daily Journal (Director of Athletics Position)
      Horse Races (See Also, Brown, Fred)
      Hotel Metropole, Budapest, Hungary (unsigned note re: swimming contest)
      Hoyt, H.H. (No Class B Yacht Races/Chairman, Yachting Committee)
      Huber, Oskar, Corresondence with Kerrigan
      Hutchinson, Reno (Reference Maccabe Dinner/Talk)
      Hutchinson, Wm. McL. (Outpost Fencing Club)
    - Indian Field Day - Kerns, Harry, 1905 (Box-folder 29/2)
      Indian Field Day (Officials/Order of Events)
      Inglis, M.M., Seattle Athletic Club (Various Topics)
      Isgrigg, Francis L. (Participate in Interscholastic Events)
      Jaeger, E.J. and Brothers (Medal Design)
      James Bay Athletic Association (Entry Fees/Names)
      Johnson, Albert A. (Reference Hammer Throw)
      Johnson, Jay (Program Request)
      Johnson, O.H., Pacific College (Receipt of Entry and Pass)
      Jones, J.T. (25-mile Race)
      Judge, H.E. (Pass)
      Keane, F.T., Rocksbury, Massachusetts (100-yard Sweepstake)
      Keevin, E.E., The Globe, New York (Boxing Championships)
      Kelly, Dan J. (Photos)
      Kelly, Harry, Spokane High School Athletic Association
      Kennedy, T.S. (Reference Association Foot Ball)
      Kerns, Harry N. (Schedule of Events/Registration)
    - Kerrigan, H. W., correspondence, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 29/3)
      General
      Reference Sending Teams to Olympian Games
      Amateur Athletic Union of U.S.
    - Kerrigan/Sullivan - Kuykendall, Robert, 1905 (Box-folder 29/4)
      Correspondence between H. W. Kerrigan and J. E. Sullivan, Amateur Athletic Union
      Kinell, Capt Edw, Commandant, Pullman Agricultural College
      Kivett, W.R. (No Boys Races)
      Knox, Chas. L. (Bicycle Race on Nevada Day)
      Knox, W.R. (Entry Blank)
      Kuykendall, Robert K. (Entry in Racing Events)
    - LaCrosse Club - Lucas, Charles, 1905 (Box-folder 29/5)
      LaCrosse Clubs, List of
      Ladd, Chas. (Chas. Ladd Trophy)
      Ladd, Jay Wesley (Reference Mr. J.A.. Horan)
      Landel, Roy (25-mile Road Race)
      Lawrence, C.W (Appointment as Chair Cricket Committee)
      Lawrence, W.J. (Reference Handicap Events)
      Lawton, A.A., Pacific Athletic Association of the Amateur Athletic Union (Ref Chas. Parsons)
      Leather, F. (Fencing Championships)
      Lewis & Lewis (Reference Bill)
      Lewis, L. Allen (Reference Trophy)
      Liginger, Walter H./Kerrigan Correspondence (Various Topics) 1 of 2
      Liginger, Walter H./Kerrigan Correspondence (Various Topics) 2 of 2
      Livingstone, R. (Silver Cup for Fly Casting)
      Lonergan, Frank, Oregon Agricultural College (Appointment as Chair Public School/State Inter-Collegiate Athletics)
      Lucas, Charles J.P., Globe Democrat, St. Louis (Reference AAU Championship)
    - McCabe, J. B. - McPheeters, S. B., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 29/6)
      MacCabe, J.B. (Telegram Reference Chicago Meeting)
      MacKenzie, K.A.J. ($25 to Cover Cost of Silver Cup)
      Maddock, J.H., Utah Athletic Association (Track & Field Events)
      Main, Ralph E. (Reference PAA Championships/Entry Blanks)
      McArthur, C.N. (Track and Field Events)
      McCready, Mrs. J.T. (General Manager, American Inn)
      McDonald, Dale F. (York, Nebraska Public Schools (Program)
      McDonald, R.R. (Log Rolling Contest)
      McDonnell/Kerrigan Correspondence (Commander of the Guard)
      McEvoy, Wm.J. (No Travel Expenses)
      McIsaac, Colin H. (Walla Walla Baseball Game)
      McIver, J.L. (Rock Drilling contest)
      McKenzie, W.R. (Bureau of Athletics Expenses)
      McKinnie, W.D. (Compete in Track Events)
      McLean, Ned, Walla Walla, Washington (Hose Races)
      McPheeters, S.B., Care Department Physical Culture (Employment)
    - Mero, E. B. - Montgomery, H. M., 1905 (Box-folder 29/7)
      Mero, E.B., American Gymnasia Company (Programs)
      Merrill, E.S., Associated Students Occidental College Reference 100-yard Dash
      Meyers, Gus (Rock Drilling Contest)
      Military Field Day/Events (Referees/Schedule/Printing)
      Miller, Arthur (Program/Entry Blanks)
      Milwaukee Sentinel (Reference Amateur Athletic Union Games)
      Mitchell, H.L., YMCA, Montesano, WA (Info Request)
      Mitchell, Harry E. (Soldiers Field Day/Various Topics)
      Mock, Guston, Montesano, WA (Reference Jensen and Fencing Championships)
      Montgomery, H.M. (Scratch the Navy Sports/Appointment as Chair Committee on Naval Sports)
    - Moore, H. H. - O'Sullivan, J. B., 1905 (Box-folder 29/8)
      Moore, H.H., YMCA Chicago (Info Request)
      Morris, T.C., Spokane Washington (Reference 100-yard Dash)
      Morrow, R.G. (Reference Michigan University)
      Morton, Will F. (Appointment as Chair, Canoeing, Swimming and Diving)
      Moulton [?], E. W. (track and field events, employment request)
      Murphy, C.G. (Appointment as Chair, Golf Tournament/Medals)
      Murray, W.L. (Pass)
      Nash, W.F., The World (Publicity New York)
      North Central Track Team Entries
      North Pacific Planing Mill Company (Bill)
      Notices Sent Out Reference Athletic Events
      Nywening, John, Manager, Chemawa BB Team
      Oakland High School (Interscholastic Relay Races)
      Oberholtzer, Herbert I. (Entering Races)
      O'Callaghan, E., Vancouver, B.C. Athletic Club (Track and Field Events)
      O'Connor, John Jay (Reference $175 Expense Bill)
      Officials for Friday and Saturday Events (Invitations)
      Officials for Public School Games, June 9 and Handicap Events June 10
      Officials for Public School Games
      Olympic Club, San Francisco, California
      Onondaga Aquatic Amusement Company
      O'Sullivan, J.B.A.A., Victoria B.C. (AAU Membership)
    - Pacific Coast Biscuit - Price, C. H., 1905 (Box-folder 29/9)
      Pacific Coast Biscuit Company (Reference Cup/Trophy)
      Pacific Coast League Playing Dates
      Pape, Al. W. (Entry Fee Single Scull Race)
      Penwell, Roy D., Minnesota State University (Fencing Tournament)
      Perkins, W.T. (Rambler Amateur Athletic Club, Baseball Tournament)
      Peterson, Roland, Pacific University (Reference Friday/Saturday Events)
      Platt, Robt. T. (Reference Track Team New York Athletic Club)
      Portland Academy Baseball Team
      Portland Bird Company (Monkey Pictures)
      Portland High School
      Powers, H.L. (Possible Cornell Participation)
      Press Release Reference Athletics at the Centennial
      Price, C.H., YMCA, Los Angeles (Reference Cup)
    - Redman, George - Savage, C. F., 1905 (Box-folder 29/10)
      Redman, George (Swimming Events)
      Regan, James Jr. (Soldier Athletics)
      Report of Athletic Bureau
      Retzer, W.G. (Seattle Athletic Club (Reference Conference Athletics and Physical Director
      Riley, F.B. and E.F. (Reference Form on MAAC Stationary)
      Riley, Thos. F., New England Association Amateur Athletic Club
      Robb, W.A., Multnomah Athletic Club (Reference Fees)
      Robinson, Chas A. (Reference Races)
      Roller, B.F., University of Washington (Reference Entrees McDonald and Dohn)
      Rusk, R.G. (Bag Punching Contest)
      Rylance, R. (Crickett Tournament Awards)
      Sapp, Col. S., Washington Agricultural College (Reference Entry in Events)
      Sargent, Frank L. (events on Navy Day)
      Saturday Program
      Savage, C.F. (Telegram Reference Baseball Game on Dalles Day)
    - Schedule of Events - Swann, Claude, 1905 (Box-folder 29/11)
      Schedule of Events
      Seattle High School
      Seller, M. and Company (Entrees)
      Sheridan, Martin J., Greater New York Irish-American Athletic Club
      Sherman, F.W. (Bill for Launching at Sculling Races)
      Sherrill, Chas. H., New York Athletic Club (Reference Travel Rates; James Mitchell entry in weight events)
      Shogren of The Oregonian (Reference Photos)
      Smith, F.G., Stanford University (Participant)
      Smithson, Forest, OAC Track Team (Events)
      Sommenschein, Louis (Info Request)
      Stewart, A.C., Secretary Celtic Foot Ball Club, Vancouver, B.C. (Reference McDonnel)
      Stiles, H.M., Ventura, California (Programs)
      Stimson, F.C., Manager, OAC Track Team (Acknowledgment)
      Stokes, Chas.L., University of Washington (Boxing Championships)
      Stott, Plowden, Stanford University (Athletic Events)
      Stowall, Percy (Open regatta Event)
      Sullivan, Daniel A (Entry in All-around Championships)
      Swann, Claude V. (Reference Possible Multnomah Basketball Member)
    - Tacoma Football Club - Vinson, J., 1905 (Box-folder 29/12)
      Tacoma Football Club
      Taylor, J.S., Umatilla, Oregon (Races)
      Taylor, Morris (Names of Relay Race Team)
      Teal, J.N. (Passes)
      Tennis Day Program
      Thompson School Entries
      Townsend, R.M. (Postpone Horse Races)
      Trine, W.O., Oregon Agricultural College (Reference Position for Greenshaw)
      Troy, T.J. (Program Request/Handicap Games/Medal)
      Tualatin Academy (Interscholastic Relay Races)
      Union Printing Company (Requisition for Badges)
      VanCourt, D. (Reference Medals; Copper vs. Gold)
      Vernon, James M. (Reference Money Sent)
      Victoria, Canada Football Club (Reference Playing in Tournament)
      Vinson, J. (Public School Games)
    - Wakefield, John - Wirtz, Willard, 1905 (Box-folder 29/13)
      Wakefield, John A./Kerrigan Correspondence